clickxchange.com 2011-10-08

# Privacy Policy

**Disclosure of Information to Non-affiliated Trusted Third Parties**  
clickXchange Media and Affiliates ("Companies") will disclose nonpublic personal information about you to other market participants that provide goods and services. The Companies may also disclose aggregate, anonymous data to investors and potential partners based on information collected from Users. You authorize us, or a marketing partner, to contact you with exciting new offers and information, via email, automated telephone messages or SMS/Text messages to your mobile phone, even if you are listed on a Do Not Call Registry.  Users may opt out of the Companies disclosure to nonaffiliated trusted third parties (the “Parties”) by following the instructions in the opt out section of this privacy policy. We may also disclose nonpublic personal information about you as permitted by law.   

**Privacy**  
Users' privacy is very important to us. Companies are committed to safeguarding the information Users entrust to Companies. This Web site is not directed at individuals under 18 years of age. 

**Consent to Receive Privacy Notice and Opt Out Notice Via this Web Site**  
By acknowledging receipt of this privacy notice, you the customer also consent to receive your annual notice of the privacy policy, as required by FTC regulation, via this web site. By acknowledging receipt of this privacy notice, you the customer also consent to receive your opt out notice and opportunity to opt out, as required by FTC regulation, via this web site.

**The Information We Collect**  
This Privacy Policy applies to consumers that have signed up on this website and all affiliated website links and products. We may sell the personal information that you supply to us and we may work with other third party businesses to bring selected retail opportunities to our members via direct mail, email, telemarketing and SMS, together with ancillary offers, programs and services from those companies. These businesses may include providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation and email marketing.

Companies may collect nonpublic personal information from User in a variety of ways, including online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where Users are invited to volunteer such information. The type of information we collect from consumers includes, but is not limited to: Name, Last Name, Address1, Address2, City, State, Zip Code, Phone Number, Email Address, IP Address, TimeDate Stamp and any information required to process an application to receive the product being offered within the site.

Companies may also collect information about how Users use our Web site, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the Web site or the domains from which Users originate. We may use "cookies" to track how Users use our Web site. A cookie is a piece of software that a Web server can store on the Users' PC and use to identify the Users should they visit the Web site again. While not all of the information that we collect from Users is nonpublic personal information, it may be associated with nonpublic personal information that Users provide us through our Web site.

This website, websites linking to this website, and websites linked from this website (collectively "We") may make available a service either directly or through the Parties by which you can receive messages on your wireless device via short message service ("SMS Service"). Your provider's standard data and messaging rates apply to all SMS correspondence. All charges are billed by and payable to your mobile service provider. You represent that you are 18 years of age and the owner or authorized user of the wireless device on which messages will be received, and that you are authorized to approve the applicable charges. Data obtained from you in connection with this SMS Service may include your name, address, cell phone number, your provider's name, and the date, time, and content of your messages. The use of this information will be in accordance with this Mobile Policy. If fees are charged to your wireless account invoice, we may provide your carrier with your applicable information in connection therewith. Your wireless carrier and other service providers may also collect data about your wireless device usage, and their practices are governed by their own policies. You acknowledge and agree that the SMS Service is provided via wireless systems which use radios (and other means) to transmit communications over complex networks. We will not be liable for any delays in the receipt of any SMS messages, as delivery is subject to effective transmission from your network operator. SMS message services are provided on an AS IS basis. We do not guarantee that your use of the SMS Service will be private or secure, and we are not liable to you for any lack of privacy or security you may experience. You are fully responsible for taking precautions and providing security measures best suited for your situation and intended use of the SMS Service. You may opt out of the SMS Service at any time by replying "STOP", "END", or "QUIT" to the SMS text message you have received. This process impacts only the future delivery of the particular SMS message offering, so you must send that message for each offering.

By accepting of the privacy policy and terms and conditions of this website (and any associated offers, contests, giveaways or other programs), and providing your telephone number, you are subscribing to a service that transmits information concerning various special product offers to subscribers using pre-recorded voice messages.

By subscribing, you are expressly consenting to receive prerecorded telephone messages from Platinum Online Group, Firebrand Group, S.A., LLC, doing business as Worldwide Commerce Associates (“WCA”), and Education and Degree Partners, and the Parties that provide information concerning the availability of various goods and services. The calls you are agreeing to receive are solely descriptive in nature, and any goods or services described in the call are not sold by or through WCA. You are subscribing to receive calls only from WCA, and only at the specific number(s) you have provided to us. Your consent will be effective if the number you have provided is a home, business, or cell phone line, or if the number is registered on any state or federal Do-Not-Call (DNC) list as of the date of this consent. This consent shall remain in effect until you revoke your consent and cancel your subscription.

**How We Use Information**  
Companies collect nonpublic personal information from its Users in order to match Users with lenders and brokers. By submitting the application, Users consent to the disclosure of their nonpublic personal information to these lenders and brokers. The lenders and brokers may contact you directly after they receive your nonpublic personal information. Companies may also use information collected through our web site for research regarding the effectiveness of the web site and Company’s marketing and advertising efforts.

**Maintenance of Information & Security**  
Information about Users that is maintained on our systems is protected using industry standard security measures that includes but is not limited to security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All data is protected using the most advanced methods available. We do not store financial information, credit card numbers or personal information like social security numbers on this Web site. However, due to the nature of the Internet, computer networks, systems and other factors, we cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on, or transmitted from our systems will be completely secure.

**Use of IP Addresses**  
An IP (Internet Protocol) address is a number that is assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. Your IP address does not contain any nonpublic personal information about you. Companies collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregate information to our advertisers, and to ensure the validity of customer requests.

**Web Site Links**  
This Web site may contain links to other Internet web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Internet web sites.

**Opt Out Notice and Opportunity to Opt-Out**  
Companies may disclose nonpublic personal information about you the customer to nonaffiliated Parties, as previously described in this privacy policy. You have the right to opt out of this disclosure at any time before or after you submit nonpublic personal information. If you wish to opt out, please 

1\. Click this link to electronically opt-out.

OR 

2\. Please print a copy of the ad that you received and send it along with a letter indicating your desire to opt-out, to: 

clickXchange Media   
PO Box 515381 #36370  
Los Angeles, CA 90051-6681  
Remove my e-mail address from this advertisement.

OR 

3\. By calling 800-269-0281 or 877-351-1154

4\. Send “STOP”, “END”, or “QUIT” to the SMS text message you have received and we will remove your personal information within 10 days of receiving such request. By completing or submitting a registration form or partial registration form you are consenting to receive SMS, wireless or other mobile offering to your cell phone. You understand that your wireless carrier's standard charges and rates apply to these messages.
